Guide to the Papers of Jefferson Davis documents and reference collection, 1815-2015 MS 638
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Newspapers (originals) and general images, 1861-1894
  - Portraits of Major-General James McAllister Schofield and Brigadier General Augustus L. Chetlain. Harper's Weekly, p. 213. April 2, 1864. (Drawer 117, Item 11)
  - First of April, 1864. Harper's Weekly. April 2, 1864. (Drawer 117, Item 12)
  - European Iron-clads. Harper's Weekly, p. 220. April 2, 1864. (Drawer 117, Item 13)
  - Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XX, no. 501. New York [assassination and funeral of President Abraham Lincoln] May 6, 1865. (Drawer 117, Item 14)
  - Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XX. no. 505. New York, June 3, 1865. (Drawer 117, Item 15)
  - Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XLV, no. 1,170. New York, March, 2, 1878. (Drawer 117, Item 16)
  - Recapture from the Rebels of the Schooner Enchantress by the U.S. Steamer Albatross. (Drawer 117, Item 17)
  - The secession masked battery near Vienna, VA. (Drawer 117, Item 18)
  - Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XII, no. 299. New York, Aug. 10, 1861. (Drawer 117, Item 19)
  - New York Illustrated News, vol. IV, no. 94. New York, Aug. 19, 1861. (Drawer 117, Item 20)
  - War Supplement. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XIV, no. 347. New York, May 31, 1862. (Drawer 117, Item 21)
  - Harper's Weekly: A Journal of Civilization, vol. VIII, no. 379. New York, April 2, 1864. (Drawer 117, Item 22)
  - Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, vol. XX, no. 509. New York, July 1, 1865. (Drawer 117, Item 23)
  - Harper's Weekly: Journal of Civilization, vol. IX, no. 442. New York, June 17, 1865. (Drawer 117, Item 24)
  - Harper's Weekly: Journal of Civilization, vol. XIV, no. 714. New York, Sept. 3, 1870. (Drawer 117, Item 25)
  - Harper's Weekly: Journal of Civilization, vol. XX, no. 1038. New York, Nov. 18, 1876. (Drawer 117, Item 26)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 2, part II. April 2, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 27)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 3, part III. April 9, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 28)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 4, part IV. April 16, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 29)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 5, part V. April 23, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 30)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 6, part VI. April 30, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 31)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 7, part VII. May 7, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 32)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 8, part VIII. May 14, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 33)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 9, part IX. May 21, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 34)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 10, part X. May 28, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 35)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 11, part XI. June 4, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 36)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 12, part XII. June 11, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 37)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 13, part XIII. June 18, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 38)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 14, part XIV. June 25, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 39)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol 1, no. 15, part XV. July 2, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 40)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol 1, no. 16, part XVI. July 9, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 41)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 17, part XVII. July 16, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 42)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 18, part XVIII. July 23, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 43)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 19, part XIX. July 30, 1894. (Drawer 117, Item 44)
  - The Century War Book. Battles and Leaders of the Civil War. People's Pictorial Edition. The Century Series, vol. 1, no. 20, part XX. Aug. 6, 1894 (Drawer 117, Item 45)
  - Hood's Texas Brigade reunion. 2 photographs, no dates. Some individuals identified on transparent overlay. (Drawer 117, Item 46)
  - The New York Herald, page 1 "Jeff. Davis' Last Proclamation", 1865-04-15 (Drawer 117, Item 47)
- Series IV: Maps, 1819-1995
  - Battle of Buena Vista, Feb. 22-23, 1847 (vol. 3) (Drawer 117, Item 48)
  - Rio Grande and Northeastern Mexico, ca. 1846 (vol. 3) (Drawer 117, Item 49)
  - South Central US and the Rio Grande, ca. 1846 (vol. 3) (Drawer 117, Item 50)
  - Eastern Monterrey, Sept. 21-23, 1846 (vol 3) (Drawer 117, Item 51)
  - Virginia area, 1864 (vol 10) (Drawer 117, Item 52)
  - United States in 1850 (vol. 4) (Drawer 117, Item 53)
  - Central Confederate states, 1864 (vol. 10) (Drawer 117, Item 54)
  - Mississippi, 1851 (vol. 4) (Drawer 117, Item 55)
  - Mississippi/Vicksburg, 1837-1975 (vol. 14) (Drawer 117, Item 56)
  - Jefferson Davis National Highway map (Drawer 117, Item 57)
  - Warren Co., MS general highway map (Drawer 117, Item 58)
  - Bedford, MS geological survey, 1963 (Drawer 117, Item 59)
  - Somerset, LA geological survey, 1963 (Drawer 117, Item 60)
  - Mississippi River through MS counties (Drawer 117, Item 61)
  - Theater of Operations [along Mississippi River] showing Vicksburg campaign, 1863 (Drawer 117, Item 62)
  - Growth of MS counties (Drawer 117, Item 63)
  - New map of Mississippi with its roads and distances, 1850 (Drawer 117, Item 64)
  - Mississippi, 1845 (Drawer 117, Item 65)
  - Davis Island (Drawer 117, Item 66)
  - Topographical view of Rock Island in the Mississippi River, 1819 (Drawer 117, Item 67)
  - Fort Gibson (Drawer 117, Item 68)
  - Potomoc Ricer from Brunswick to VanDeventer's Island & environs of Sugarloaf, Poolesville, Leesburg, Waterford & the German Settlement, 1995 (Drawer 117, Item 69)
  - Plates from Official Records Atlas (inventory in map drawer) (Drawer 116, Item 1-175)
- Series V: Addendum
  - Duplicate microfilm (26) (Box 40, Item 1 - 26)